

Shibly Qureshi

Administration | Customer Service | Branch Management | MBA & BBA

Career Objective

Pursuing a challenging mid-level opportunities in operation or customer service department, preferably demanding any suitable responsibility of branch management, in any renowned organization and grow rapidly with increasing responsibilities.

Contact Info

+880 1770937170

shibly.qureshi@gmail.com

in www.linkedin.com/in/shibly-qureshi-/

B-2/F-17, Shantikunjo, Zoo Road, Mirpur 1, Dhaka

Academic Qualification

EMBA in North South University
Human Resource Management
3.03 out of 4.00 Year: 2022

BBA in University of Asia Pacific Finance

3.58 out of 4.00 Year: 2011

HSC in Business Studies

Dhaka Board

4.50 out of 5.00 Year: 2007

SSC in Science

Sylhet Board

3.94 out of 5.00 Year: 2005

Expertise

Administration

General Accounts Operation

S Cost & Budget Management

People Management

Sales Operation

Customer Service Management

Customer Relationship Management

Training & Development

Career Summary

Around 8 years experienced operation, customer service and branch management professional with having expertise on administration, general accounts operation, cost & budget preparation people management, sales operation, customer service management, customer relationship management and training & development.

Job Experience

Office Manager- Admin

(March 2022- Present)

Alesha Engineering & Services Limited

Core Function:

- Ensure smooth operational activities and keep record
- Organize and coordinate office operational activities
- ➤ Main relationship with all stake holder of AESL
- ➤ Monitor project activities and take corrective action wherever required
- > Prepare monthly report and present to concern authority.

Office Manager- Admin

(September 2021-February 2022)

Alesha Mart Limited

Core Function:

- Establish and implement office procedures and practices
- ➤ Attend to general issues and fixing simple problems
- > Interact with clients and merchant.
- > Organize and coordinate office operational activities.

Associate, Omni Channel Business Operation

(Nov 2014 – Feb 2020)

UAE Exchange Center LLC, UAE

Core Function:

- Supervised and motivate operation team to ensure maximum productivity.
- > Evaluated branch performance periodically
- > Set individual and branch sales target for each quarter

Skills

© Communication

Teamwork

Leadership Skill

Adaptability

Presentation Skill Time Management

Computer

MS Word : Advance Level

: Proficient MS Excel

MS PowerPoint : Adroit

Language

Bengali: Native

English: Good Working Knowledge

Personal Info

Father's Name: Dr. Humayun Kabir Qureshi

Mother's Name: Taruna Qureshi

Date of Birth: 7th September, 1989

Nationality : Bangladeshi

NID : 509 113 4139

Recommendations

Mr. Azizul Hassan Satter, FCA

Director, ESS & Partners

Managing Partner, Jobair Satter & Co.

Contact no: +88 0 172 907 1250

Email: a.satter@essadvisory.com

Mr. Rubaiyat-E-Ashique

Deputy Secretary, Cabinet Division People's Republic of Bangladesh

Email: reashique71@yahoo.com

Declaration

I, Shibly Qureshi, hereby declare that the information contained herein is true and correct to the best of my knowledge and belief.

Shibly Qureshi

- Trained & developed the staffs about products and business
- Ensure the effective execution of day to day office administrative issues.
- ➤ Maintained good relations with the stakeholders
- > Maintained proper documentation & reporting.
- Maintain relation Law enforcement authority and ensure all licenses and legal documentation are up to date.

Assistant Customer Service, Branch Operations

UAE Exchange Center LLC, UAE

(Feb 2012 – Oct 2014)

Core Functions:

- > Provided front line services to the customers
- Maintained a good relationship with customers
- > Dealt with and solved customer problems

Achievements:

- ➤ Got Service Excellence Award
- Achieved ACPP (Annual Corporate Planning Process) target for consecutive 02 years.

Training

On the job training from UAE Exchange Centre LLC:

➤ Customer Service & Sales Training

Duration: 01 Day

Compliance & Risk

Duration: 01 Day

Training obtained from Cisco Networking Academy:

> Introduction to Cyber security Online training from GP Academy

Training obtained from Standard Chartered Bank:

Customer Due Diligence

Duration: 01 Day

> Sanctions

Duration: 01 Day

➤ Anti-Money Laundering and Counter Terrorist Financing

Duration: 01 Day

Training obtained from The Corporate Coach:

➤ Sales Mastery- Proven Corporate B2B sales strategies & **Techniques**

Duration: 03 Days

Training obtained from Spike Story:

> Branding Through Digital Marketing Duration: 03 Days

Training obtained from SME foundation:

> E-Commerce for SME's

Duration: 03 Days

Volunteer Activities: Bangladesh Red Crescent Society (3 months)

Covid- 19 Vaccination Program